<Publish>
	<ModId Value="78187" />
	<DisplayName Value="RealisticDensity" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Elevate your city's realism and challenge! Boost job numbers across zones and vital buildings." />
	<LongDescription>
# RealisticDensity

Have you always been annoyed that you have to build such large industrial areas? Or that your business takes up almost as much space as your residential areas?
Why a power plant only has 10 employees or a high school with 2000 students only employs a handful of teachers?

**Then this mod is just right for you.**

## Important Note
This mod is originally created by **89pleasure**. He has given me permission to maintain and continue development on this mod.

## Features:
- Increased employee numbers for Commercial, Industrial, and Office zones
- Increased employee numbers for service buildings such as schools, hospitals, clinics, power plants, police, fire stations, cargo train terminals, and harbors
- Employee numbers of existing buildings remain unchanged
- Higher difficulty level due to increased worker and cargo traffic and demand for well planned public transport routes
- More storages will fill your industry zones and create a more realistic and diverse look
- More crowded city streets and more traffic

## Planned Features:
- Add UI to change the intensity of the mod
- Increased numbers for high density residential buildings
- Increased employee numbers for public transport buildings
- Increased employee numbers for unique buildings

## Important Information:
- **The mod is currently in the BETA phase - so problems can therefore occur**
- **The mod is currently activated globally for all your cities!**
- **It has an impact on your save game and can possibly break your city**
- This mod has an impact on the performance of the game (by design)
- It is recommended to use the mod in a new city
- However, it is possible to use the mod in an existing city, as it does not alter the employee numbers of already existing buildings

## Credits
- Thanks **optimus-code** for his C# knowledge and help

## Special thanks to:
- **Susanne**, **Bruceyboy24804**, **Woovie**, **Rebecca** and **mad** for their testing and feedback

## License:
- This mod is subject to the GNU license. Please read the license terms before using the mod.

**Thank you for using the RealisticDensity Mod!**
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/realistic-density.1682055/" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.1.3" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<ChangeLog>
- Corrected Settings location
	</ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/Fc6KuuBkRr" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/kosch104/cities2-realistic-density" />
</Publish>